A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Press Releases, Series 13 FA382
Rockefeller Archive Center
- October 13, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 476)
  Portland, Oregon, General Reception
- October 14, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 477)
  Seattle, Washington, Press Conference
- October 14, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 478)
  Seattle, Washington, Seattle Today Show Interview
- October 14, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 479)
  Seattle, Washington, John Spellman Volunteer Breakfast
- October 14, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 480)
- October 14, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 481)
- October 14, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 482)
  Seattle, Washington, John Nance Garner Rally
- October 18, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 483)
  Grand Rapids, Michigan, Hal Sawyer Luncheon
- October 18, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 484)
  Grand Rapids, Michigan, Remarks at Airport
- October 18, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 485)
  Grand Rapids, Michigan, LUNCH WITH ROCKY
- October 18, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 486)
  Detroit, Michigan, Channel 4 Taping
- October 18, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 487)
  Detroit, Michigan, Fund Raiser
- October 18, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 488)
  Saginaw, Michigan, Reception - Remarks
- October 18, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 489)
  Kalamazoo, Michigan, Fund Raising Lunch
- October 18, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 490)
  Detroit, Michigan, Fund Raising Dinner
- October 18, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 491)
  Detroit, Michigan, Press Michigan
- October 18, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 492)
  Saginaw, Michigan, Press Conference
- October 18, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 493)
  Kalamazoo, Michigan, Press Conference
- October 19, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 494)
  Bloomington, Minnesota, Cabana Court Reception
- October 19, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 495)
  Bloomington, Minnesota, Henry Wolfe Taping
- October 19, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 496)
  Bloomington, Minnesota, Elephant Club Reception Lunch
- October 19, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 497)
  Bloomington, Minnesota, Press Conference
- October 19, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 498)
  Bloomington, Minnesota, Candidate Rally Remarks
- October 19, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 499)
  Minneapolis, Minnesota, Elephant Club Remarks
- October 20, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 500)
  Washington, DC Joan Braden Q&A
- October 20, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 501)
  Washington, DC Joan Braden, VP Remarks
- October 26, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 502)
  Washington, DC National Press Club Remarks
- October 27, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 503)
  Long Island, New York, Senior Citizens Rally Remarks
- October 27, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 504)
  Long Island, New York, Senior Citizens Press Conference
- October 27, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 505)
  Hempstead, New York, Business Leaders Dinner
- October 27, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 506)
  Hempstead, New York, Student Center Complex Remarks
- October 27, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 507)
  Island Park, New York, Republican Rally
- October 27, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 508)
  Franklin Square, New York, Women's Tea
- October 27, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 509)
  Franklin Square, Senior Citizens Rally
- October 27, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 510)
  Long Island, New York Release
- November 5, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 511)
  Release of Texts of Letters from VP to President-Elect Carter
- November 5, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 512)
  Release Texts of Letter from VP to VP-Elect Mondale
- November 5, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 513)
  Exchange of Remarks Between President and VP
- November 7, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 514)
  Eulogy for Gus Levy
- November 9, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 515)
  Interview with U.S. News and World Report
- November 12, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 516)
  Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg Foundation Dinner
- November 16, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 517)
  Washington, DC, Conference on Future of Productivity
- November 16, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 518)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Defense Advisory Committee On Women in Services
- November 16, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 519)
  Washington, DC, Republican Eagles Luncheon
- November 17, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 520)
  Pocantico Hills, New York, Kykuit National Historic Landmark, History and speech by Thomas S. Kleppe
- November 18, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 521)
  Williamsburg, Virginia, 22nd Annual Session of the North Atlantic Treaty
- November 16, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 522)
  Washington, DC, Remarks to 10 Outstanding Young American Women
- November 21, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 523)
  Tarrytown, New York, Briefing by John Mulliken on Dedication Ceremony of John D. Rockefeller Estate
- November 21, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 524)
  Pocantico Hills, New York, Remarks at Dedication Ceremony of John D. Rockefeller Estate
- November 30, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 525)
  New York City, New York, Fiftieth Anniversary of the China Institute
- December 2, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 526)
  Letter to Peter Peterson Re: Executive Salaries
- December 9, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 527)
  Washington, DC, Exchange of Remarks Between VP and Governor John Connally
- December 15, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 528)
  Washington, DC, Mount Vernon College Political Science Association
- December 2, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 529)
  Washington, DC, 100th Anniversary of Pakistan's Founder's Birth
- December 8, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 530)
  Washington, DC, Georgetown University Graduate Student Forum
- December 12, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 531)
  Text of Letters to Mrs. Richard J. Daley
- January 12, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 532)
  Washington, DC, President's Awards for Distinguished Federal Civil Service
- January 13, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 533)
  Press Release: Appointments in Press Office
- January 18, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 534)
  Washington, DC, Remarks to the Members of the U.S. Senate
- Trip Files - January 23, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 535)
  Chicago, Illinois, National Business Leadership Conference
- Trip Files - January 29, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 536)
  Millburn, New Jersey, Republican Finance Committee Dinner
- Trip Files - February 13, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 537)
  New York City, New York, Salute to the Vice President Dinner
- Trip Files - February 26, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 538)
  Detroit, Michigan, Society of Automotive Engineers
- Trip Files - March 25-28, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 539)
  Saudi Arabia, King Faisal Funeral
- Trip Files - April 2, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 540)
  Niagara Falls, New York, Senator Bridges Funeral
- Trip Files - April 9, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 541)
  New Orleans, Louisiana, American Newspaper Publishers
- Trip Files - April 13-17, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 542)
  Taiwan, Vice President's Trip re: funeral of Chiang-Kai-Shek
- Trip Files - April 13-17, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 543)
- Trip Files - April 18, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 544)
  Boca Raton, Florida, Young Presidents Organization
- Trip Files - April 18, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 545)
- Trip Files - May 9, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 546)
  Hot Springs, Virginia, Business Counsel Meeting
- Trip Files - June 4, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 547)
  Annapolis, Maryland Trip
- Trip Files - June 12, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 548)
  New York City, Republican Committee Luncheon Dinner
- Trip Files - June 23-July 8, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 549)
  Vice President's Trip to: London, Germany, Austria
- Trip Files - July 9, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 550)
  Atlanta, Georgia, National Commission on Water Quality
- Trip Files - July 12, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 551)
  Hanover, New Hampshire, Victor Borella's Memorial Service
- Trip Files - July 22, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 552)
  Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, Productivity Commission Meeting
- Trip Files - July 22, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 553)
  Cincinnati, Ohio, Midwest Governor's Conference
- Trip Files - August 26-27, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 554)
  Alabama and North Carolina
- Trip Files - September 5, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 555)
  Rochester and Greece, New York
- Trip Files - September 12-13, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 556)
  Dallas, Little Rock and Oklahoma
- Trip Files - September 12-13, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 557)
- Trip Files - September 14-15, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 558)
  London, England
- Trip Files - September 3, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 559)
  VP's trip to Oregon
- Trip Files - October 2, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 560)
  Portland, Oregon, Western States Republican Conference
- Trip Files - October 7, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 561)
  Kings Mountain, North Carolina
- Trip Files - October 11, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 562)
  Newport News, Virginia Ship Launching
- Trip Files - October 15-16, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 563)
  Columbus, Ohio, Charleston, West Virginia and Roanoke, Va.
- Trip Files - October 15-16, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 564)
  Columbus, Ohio, Charleston, West Virginia and Roanoke, Virginia
- Trip Files - October 21, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 565)
  Denver, Colorado, Domestic Council Forum
- Trip Files - October 21, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 566)
- Trip Files - October 23-24, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 567)
  Indiana, Illinois, and Wisconsin
- Trip Files - October 23-24, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 568)
- Trip Files - October 29, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 569)
  Tampa, St. Petersburg Domestic Council Forum (Florida)
- Trip Files - October 29, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 570)
- Trip Files - November 11, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 571)
  Austin, Texas, Domestic Council Forum
- Trip Files - November 11, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 572)
- Trip Files - November 14-15, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 573)
  Kansas City, Illinois, St. Paul, Minneapolis
- Trip Files - November 18, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 574)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Domestic Council Forum
- Trip Files - November 18, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 575)
- Trip Files - November 20-21, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 576)
  Wichita, Kansas, Republican Governors Conference
- Trip Files - November 25, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 577)
  Indianapolis, Indiana, Domestic Council Forum
- Trip Files - December 4, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 578)
- Trip Files - December 5, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 579)
  New York City, National Association of Manufacturers
- Trip Files - December 8-9, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 580)
  Los Angeles, California, Domestic Council Forum
- Trip Files - December 8-9, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 581)
- Trip Files - December 9, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 582)
  Los Angeles Convention Center
- Trip Files - December 11-12, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 583)
  Nashville, Tennessee and Houston, Texas - GOP
- Trip Files - January 26, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 584)
  Salem, West Virginia, Trip
- Trip Files - January 30, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 585)
  Dearborn, Michigan, Midwest Republican Conference
- Trip Files - February 12, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 586)
  Lexington and Louisville, Kentucky
- Trip Files - February 20, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 587)
  Lansing, Michigan Lincoln Day Dinner
- Trip Files - February 23, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 588)
  Boston, Massachusetts, American Association for the Advancement of Science
- Trip Files - March 16-17, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 589)
  Chicago, Illinois, Grocers and Executive Club
- Trip Files - March 12, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 590)
  Albuquerque, New Mexico, Lincoln Day Dinner
- Trip Files - March 20-April 4, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 591)
  Vice President's Trip Around the World: Tunis, Tunisia, Iran, Kuala Lampur, Singapore, Bali, Indonesia, New Zealand, Tahiti, Australia, Paris
- Trip Files - March 20-April 4, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 0591A)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restricted material
- Trip Files - April 12, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 592)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Club of Rome
- Trip Files - April 14-15, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 593)
  Des Moines, Iowa, Atlanta, Georgia - GOP functions
- Trip Files - May 3-5, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 594)
  San Francisco/Los Angeles
- Trip Files - May 10, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 595)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
- Trip Files - May 10, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 596)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania - International Press Institute
- Trip Files - May 13-15, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 597)
  Germany, Frankfurt, Berlin
- Trip Files - May 13-15, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 598)
- Trip Files - May 20, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 599)
  Cincinnati, Ohio, PFC Reception and Dinner
- Trip Files - May 26, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 600)
  National Conference on Regulatory Reform
- Trip Files - June 2, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 601)
  Colorado Springs, Colorado, USAF Academy
- Trip Files - June 4, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 602)
  Ocean City, Maryland, GOP Convention Dinner
- Trip Files - June 18, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 603)
  Greensboro, North Carolina, GOP
- Trip Files - June 21, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 604)
  West Orange, New Jersey
- Trip Files - July 20, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 605)
  Wilmington, Delaware, 1975 Victory
- Trip Files - August 2, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 606)
  Seal Harbor, Maine, Republican State Committee Reception
- Trip Files - August 2, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 607)
- Trip Files - August 9, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 608)
  Kansas City, Missouri, RNC Platforms Hearing
- Trip Files - August 16-19, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 609)
  Kansas City, Missouri, Republican National Convention
- Trip Files - September 16, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 610)
  Buffalo, Rochester, Syracuse, Binghampton, New York City
- Trip Files - September 21-22, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 611)
  Chicago and Ohio Campaign
- Trip Files - September 28, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 612)
  New Jersey and Pennsylvania (Campaign)
- Trip Files - September 28, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 613)
- Trip Files - October 3, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 614)
  London Trip, Art Exhibit
- Trip Files - October 7, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 615)
  Chicago, Illinois, Salute to President
- Trip Files - October 12-14, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 616)
  San Francisco, California, Seattle, Washington, Portland, Oregon
- Trip Files - October 12-14, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 617)
- Trip Files - October 18-19, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 618)
  Michigan and Minnesota Campaign
- Trip Files - October 21, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 619)
  Wilmington, Delaware Trip, Reception for Senator Bill Roth
- Trip Files - October 27, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 620)
  Hempstead, Long Island Campaign
- Trip Files - November 12, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 621)
  Williamsburg, Virginia Foundation Dinner
- Trip Files - November 18, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 622)
  Williamsburg, Virginia, NATO Assembly
- Trip Files - November 21, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 623)
  Pocantico Hills, Tarrytown, New York - Ceremony
- Trip Files - November 21, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 624)
  Tarrytown, New York, Hilton Inn, Press Briefing
- Subject Files - Abortion (Box 10, Folder 625)
- Subject Files - Anderson House (Box 10, Folder 626)
- Subject Files - Art (Box 10, Folder 627)
- Subject Files - Articles, NAR (Box 10, Folder 628)
- Subject Files - Articles, NAR (Box 10, Folder 629)
- Subject Files - Articles, NAR (Box 10, Folder 630)
- Subject Files - Articles, NAR (Box 10, Folder 631)
- Subject Files - Articles, NAR (Box 10, Folder 632)
- Subject Files - Articles, NAR (Box 10, Folder 633)
- Subject Files - Articles, NAR (Box 10, Folder 634)
- Subject Files - Articles, NAR (Box 10, Folder 635)
- Subject Files - Articles, NAR (Box 10, Folder 636)
- Subject Files - Articles, Mrs. NAR (Box 10, Folder 637)
- Subject Files - Articles, Mrs. NAR (Box 10, Folder 638)
- Subject Files - Admirals House, Vice President's Residence (Box 10, Folder 639)
- Subject Files - Admirals House, Vice President's Residence (Box 10, Folder 640)
- Subject Files - Admirals House, Vice President's Residence (Box 10, Folder 641)
- Subject Files - Admirals House, Vice President's Residence (Box 10, Folder 642)
- Subject Files - Admirals House, Vice President's Residence (Box 10, Folder 643)
- Subject Files - Attica (Box 10, Folder 644)
- Subject Files - Bicentennial (Box 10, Folder 645)
- Subject Files - Bicentennial (Box 10, Folder 646)
- Subject Files - Bicentennial (Box 10, Folder 647)
- Subject Files - Biographies, NAR (Box 11, Folder 648)
- Subject Files - Biographies, Mrs. NAR (Box 11, Folder 649)
- Subject Files - Biographies, Staff (Box 11, Folder 650)
- Subject Files - Campaign (Box 11, Folder 651)
- Subject Files - Campaign (Box 11, Folder 652)
- Subject Files - Christmas List Press 1975 and 1976 (Box 11, Folder 653)
- Subject Files - Christmas List Press 1975 and 1976 (Box 11, Folder 654)
- Subject Files - CIA Commission (Box 11, Folder 655)
- Subject Files - CIA Press Clippings (Box 11, Folder 656)
- Subject Files - CIA Press Clippings (Box 11, Folder 657)
- Subject Files - CIA Press Clippings (Box 11, Folder 658)
- Subject Files - CIA Press Clippings (Box 11, Folder 659)
- Subject Files - CIA Press Clippings (Box 11, Folder 660)
- Subject Files - CIA Press Clippings (Box 11, Folder 661)
- Subject Files - CIA Press Releases (Box 11, Folder 662)
- Subject Files - Campaign, Convention (Box 11, Folder 663)
- Subject Files - Campaign, Convention (Box 11, Folder 664)
- Subject Files - Commission on Critical Choices (Box 11, Folder 665)
- Subject Files - Commission on Critical Choices (Box 11, Folder 666)
- Subject Files - Domestic Council Letters, 12/15/75-12/16/75 (Box 11, Folder 667)
- Subject Files - Domestic Council Letters, 12/15/75-12/16/75 (Box 11, Folder 668)
- Subject Files - Domestic Council and Domestic Council Press Releases (Box 12, Folder 669)
- Subject Files - Domestic Council and Domestic Council Press Releases (Box 12, Folder 670)
- Subject Files - Domestic Council and Domestic Council Press Releases (Box 12, Folder 671)
- Subject Files - Domestic Council and Domestic Council Press Releases (Box 12, Folder 672)
- Subject Files - Dyslexia (Box 12, Folder 673)
- Subject Files - Dyslexia (Box 12, Folder 674)
- Subject Files - Earthquakes, MIT California (Box 12, Folder 675)
- Subject Files - Energy Independence Authority (Box 12, Folder 676)
- Subject Files - Energy Independence Authority (Box 12, Folder 677)
- Subject Files - Evans-Novak Political Reports (Box 12, Folder 678)
- Subject Files - Federal Compensation Panel (Box 12, Folder 679)
- Subject Files - Federal Election Commission (Box 12, Folder 680)
- Subject Files - Federalist Papers (Box 12, Folder 681)
- Subject Files - Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board (Box 12, Folder 682)
- Subject Files - Future of Freedoms Proof (Box 12, Folder 683)
- Subject Files - Future of Freedoms Proof (Box 12, Folder 684)
- Subject Files - Gellman Interview (Box 12, Folder 685)
- Subject Files - Gubernatorial Campaign - 1966-1970 New York City (Box 12, Folder 686)
- Subject Files - House Warming (Box 12, Folder 687)
- Subject Files - House Warming (Box 12, Folder 688)
- Subject Files - House Warming - Guest List (Box 12, Folder 689)
- Subject Files - IBEC (Box 12, Folder 690)
- Subject Files - Inaugural Medals (Box 12, Folder 691)
- Subject Files - Inauguration Day Ceremony (Box 13, Folder 692)
- Subject Files - Interviews with Vice President (Box 13, Folder 693)
- Subject Files - Interviews with Vice President (Box 13, Folder 694)
- Subject Files - Jackson/Rockefeller Issue (Box 13, Folder 695)
- Subject Files - Japanese House/Emperor Hirohito and Empress Nagak of Japan Visit, October 1975 (Box 13, Folder 696)
- Subject Files - Kramers/Roberts Book (Box 13, Folder 697)
- Subject Files - Al Moscow (Box 13, Folder 698)
- Subject Files - Murphy Commission (Box 13, Folder 699)
- Subject Files - National Press Club Record (Box 13, Folder 700)
- Subject Files - Nursing Home, Moreland Act Commission/Statements (Box 13, Folder 701)
- Subject Files - Nursing Home, Moreland Act Commission/Statements (Box 13, Folder 702)
- Subject Files - Nursing Home, Moreland Act Commission/Statements (Box 13, Folder 703)
- Subject Files - New York City Aid (Box 13, Folder 704)
- Subject Files - Photos, Miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 705)
- Subject Files - Pocantico Ceremony Designating Site as National Historic Landmark (Box 13, Folder 706)
- Subject Files - Politics (Box 13, Folder 707)
- Subject Files - Politics (Box 13, Folder 708)
- Subject Files - Population (Box 13, Folder 709)
- Subject Files - November 6, 1975 - VP Press Conference (Box 13, Folder 710)
- Subject Files - Press Part, Foxhall Road Residence, July 23, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 711)
- Subject Files - President's Quotes on Vice President (Box 13, Folder 712)
- Subject Files - President's Quotes on Vice President (Box 13, Folder 713)
- Subject Files - Privacy Committee (Box 14, Folder 714)
- Subject Files - Press, Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 715)
- Subject Files - Productivity, National Commission On (Box 14, Folder 716)
- Subject Files - Reagan/Rhodesia (Box 14, Folder 717)
- Subject Files - NAR Records (Box 14, Folder 718)
- Subject Files - Republican National Committee (Box 14, Folder 719)
- Subject Files - Resumes Sent to Hugh Morrow (Box 14, Folder 720)
- Subject Files - Revenue Sharing (Box 14, Folder 721)
- Subject Files - Rockefeller, Service on Government Service Commission (Box 14, Folder 722)
- Subject Files - Rockefeller Record (Box 14, Folder 723)
- Subject Files - Rockefeller Staff (Box 14, Folder 724)
- Subject Files - "The Rockefellers" - Collier and Horowitz (Box 14, Folder 726)
- Subject Files - "Rockefeller Syndrome" (Box 14, Folder 725)
- Subject Files - Rule XXII (Box 14, Folder 727)
- Subject Files - Security (Box 14, Folder 728)
- Subject Files - Staff Memorandum/Procedures (Box 14, Folder 729)
- Subject Files - Staff Memorandum/Procedures (Box 14, Folder 730)
- Subject Files - Staff Memorandum/Procedures (Box 14, Folder 731)
- Subject Files - Staff Memorandum/Procedures (Box 14, Folder 732)
- Subject Files - Science Advisory Office - White House (Box 14, Folder 733)
- Subject Files - State of the Union (Box 14, Folder 734)
- Subject Files - State of the Union (Box 14, Folder 735)
- Subject Files - STATUS - Census Bureau (Box 14, Folder 736)
- Subject Files - Swearing-In Ceremony (Box 14, Folder 737)
- Subject Files - Taxes - NAR (Box 14, Folder 738)
- Subject Files - Texas Property (Box 14, Folder 739)
- Subject Files - Venezuela Property (Box 14, Folder 740)
- Subject Files - Vice-Presidential Seal (Box 14, Folder 741)
- Subject Files - Vice-Presidential - General (Box 14, Folder 742)
- Subject Files - Withdrawal Announcement, 1976 Presidential Race, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 743)
- Subject Files - January 28, 1976 - VP Salute to President, New York City (Box 14, Folder 744)
- Subject Files - Water Quality Commission (Box 14, Folder 745)
- Subject Files - Water Quality Commission (Box 14, Folder 746)
- Subject Files - Water Quality Commission (Box 14, Folder 747)
- TV Miscellaneous - Bicentennial Minute - CBS, June 14, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 748)
- TV Miscellaneous - New York City, Face the Nation - CBS, January 26, 1975; May 30, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 749)
- TV Miscellaneous - Washington, DC, Godfrey Sperling Breakfast, September 10, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 750)
- TV Miscellaneous - Issues and Answers, ABC, November 2, 1975; May 2, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 751)
- TV Miscellaneous - Issues and Answers, ABC, June 15, 1975; May 2, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 752)
- TV Miscellaneous - Arlington, Virginia, Robert MacNeil Report, April 8, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 753)
- TV Miscellaneous - Sixty Minutes, April 18, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 754)
- TV Miscellaneous - Today Show, June 25, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 755)
- TV Miscellaneous - USIA Satellite Broadcast to Latin America, May 25, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 756)